

TIARA YULINDA PUTRI

FRESH GRADUATE

SKILLS

Programming Skill:

- HTML, CSS, JS
- PHP
- Laravel
- Vb NET.
- MySQL

Software Skill:

- Figma (UI/UX)
- Ms. Office
- Ms. Visio

CONTACT

Ponsel & WA: +62 813-9887-1645 Mail: tiarayulindaputri98@gmail.com

SOCIAL

Github: github.com/TiaraYulinda LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/tiara-yulinda Portofolio: https://tiarayulinda.github.io/

ABOUT ME

I am a Bachelor of Information System. I am a 22 years old, female. I graduated from STMIK Insan Pembangunan. I have the ability to create programs with PHP using the laravel framework. I have a good responsibility with task. Able to work in team or individually.

EDUCATION

Majoring in Information System

STMIK Insan Pembangunan | 2016 - 2020

- GPA 3.65
- Member of Executive Council Of Student

Senior High School

SMAN 19 Kab. Tangerang | 2013-2016

- Final Exam Score 84.6

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. Paragon Technology and Innovation

Production Operator | July 2020 - Oct 2020

• Ensure the quality of the products made

PT.EDS Manufacturing Indonesia

Production Operator | May, 2018 - June, 2019

- Ensure the quality of the products made
- Make product without defect

PT.Ramayana Lestari Sentosa, TBK

Chasier | May, 2017 - June, 2017

- Carry out the sales and payment process
- Keep records of all transactions
- Record physical cash and report to superiors

PROJECT

-E-learning for assigment | e-learning-ipem.epizy.com